

+398 70 498 913 kocovskamonika@yahoo.com Skopje, Macedonia 1000 LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/monikakochovska-771513197/

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a Digital Marketer with more than two years of experience in marketing. I am very passionate about working in marketing and very eager to learn about the latest digital marketing trends. I have experience with working with Facebook ads and Google ads and I am very interested in expanding my knowledge in other digital marketing platforms as well.

# **SKILLS**

- Social Media Marketing Working at Drama studio i learned a lot about Social Media and Social Media advertising which i always had interest for. I learned how to communicate with customers and give my best to leave a good impression about the company.
- Facebook Marketing While working in 6 Pro Marketing i have learned a lot about paid advertising, working with Business Manager, creating and optimizing Facebook campaigns. Working on several projects at the same time and delivering results according to the projects goals.
- Google Ads Learning and working with Google ads has been very interesting for me especially because the targeting is a bit different from Facebook so doing keyword research in order to target the right audience has been always been a interesting challenge for me.

- Research I believe that every good work starts with a good research. Research help you to get to know you clients and find the best alternatives to help them reach their goals.
- Planning I thing that for every project it is really important to know what you goal is and how to make you goal a reality, so that's why i think planning plays an important role in digital marketing.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Digital Marketer, 6 Pro Marketing, Oct 2020 - Current, Skopje, Macedonia

My responsibilities in 6 Pro Marketing are:

- Setting up Facebook campaigns for our clients;
- Daily optimizations;
- Creating new audiences in order to target the right people;
- Reports for our Facebook performance;
- Pixel documents;

Digital Marketing Intern, 6 Pro Marketing, Jul 2020 - Oct 2020, Skopje, Macedonia

In the beginnings as an intern at 6 Pro Marketing i learned the basics of marketing from how to:

- Target the right audiences;
- Optimizations;

- Create Facebook campaigns with different goals;

Sales Manager, Fluffy, Mar 2019 - May 2020, Skopje, Macedonia

My responsibilities in Fluffy were:

- Working with costumers on a daily basis;
- Managing the register;
- Training new employees;
- Motivating the employees;
- Making the working schedule;
- Finalizing stock orders;

**Public Relations Assistant, APRA Porter Novelli**, Dec 201 7 May 2018, Skopje, Macedonia Responsibilities i had working in APRA Porter Novelli:

- Writing and translating texts for clients;
- Creating post for clients social media (Facebook and Instagram);
- Doing research in interest of the company's work;

**Social Media Manager, Drama Studio**, Aug 2015 - Dec 201 5, Skopje, Macedonia My responsibilities while working for Drama studio were:

- Managing the social accounts of Drama Studio (Facebook and Instagram);
- Everyday communicating with clients who were interested in the products;

#### **EDUCATION**

Master's Degree, Managing Strategic Communications

Dec 2019

Institute of communication studies

Bachelor, Journalism Jul 2016

School of Journalism and Public Relations - Skopje, Macedonia

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Player
Strong Work Ethics
Problem-solving
Communication
Hard Working
Analysis
Diligence
Hard working